Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
The devil possessing Rone took on its true form.
It then revealed its role in the massacre and resurrection of the elves.
Patry and the Eye of the Midnight Sun were its unwitting pawns in a plot 500 years in the making.
Rampage as you please. Allow your fear and despair to be your guides.
After breaking Patry both in body and spirit, this devil turned him into a dark elf.
Hatred.
Oh no! This spell!
I know it's magic.
Thank you.
I've seen this before.
It's the spell that almost took out me and Captain Yami.
Only this time, it's even stronger.
Ghosh came in and saved us with his mirror magic back then.
But...
A tree.
He's concentrating so much magic.
How?
Hatred.
Demon-like magic.
Ray of Divine Punishment.
Perish.
But still, together, we've got this!
Charяни!
Tarяни!
Jar!
Charяни!
Char яв redundancy!
Uk глτοbeat.
Ok, we managed to survive somehow.
Summon away.
R Everest!
Appreciate the save you know that was a close call that spell was strong casting. It should have depleted his mana
I hate you
There's no way how can this be that sinister magic it just keeps welling up
Okay, even if I can't take my dark form
There's too much at stake for me to lose
Now die
Your complexion has changed, but I'll never forget that face
Leave him to me
How did he do that fair warning?
I'm not as kind as we go leon
hatred
Hatred you have no chance of besting me alone a
Conflict between wizards is decided by more than raw power
Some types of magic have intrinsic advantages over others
This is why magic knights work in teams to cover for each other's weaknesses
But nozel Silva is an exception is all-purpose magic makes him a team unto himself
With this ever-changing mercury. He's able to adapt to any situation and compete with any foe
I hate you
Your light magic is formidable, but my mercury counters it perfectly
Nozel's magic is both powerful and sophisticated
He creates a vast amount of mercury, then hardens it into mirror-like shields
That being said, I don't exactly plan on losing to the man whose magic counters mine either
In the meantime, I've been sharpening my skills, waiting for the chance to avenge him
What a理由
Captain Nozel's winning
He might be a cold-hearted jerk, but he's captain of the silver eagles for a reason
his technique's incredible still though something's up with that elf guy how is he able to move that
quickly after unleashing all of that power you're certainly a slippery rat but my preparations are
complete this spell requires all the power and focus i can muster i couldn't use it in the last
battle because my magic was being disrupted mercury creation magic silver star of execution
hatred hatred this spell will contain you and your light magic while letting me attack from any
angle it's an inescapable prison i hate you die
just die human let your unseeing rage be your end
he deflected every last blade of light such incredible precision
asta you know those are your names
the next wizard king is going to be me
earlier you said you planned to become the wizard king asta it seems that i am your rival as well
cool then i guess you're my rival too the title of wizard king is still mine
nuh-uh mine mine yeah keep talking you'll see
patrie if i had just spoken up about everything
then maybe your fate would have been different hey patrie can you hear me
it's too late it's too late i think i'm done for
goodbye patrie licked
i don't need a reason to save somebody's life even if you're my enemy when it comes down
to it our differences don't matter
damn it after all this i end up saved by human royalty
that's why i didn't want to get involved with them
they've always been like this and they always will be
well you were chosen that's true but not by the four-leaf clover
by me my little puppet
now then time to die hold up i don't feel like that's how this is supposed to play out
there's got to be another way to set things straight
and how do you suggest we settle the matter that villain is the leader of the eye of the midnight
sun his actions have thrown the clover kingdom into a state of chaos and confusion resulting in a
multitude of senseless casualties yeah i know that but please wait
this sounds odd but that isn't his own body it's actually von jence's that can't be possible
his appearance and his magic power are completely different i can't explain why but i'm positive
that i'm right i can sense captain von jence's presence so this is my suggestion let this absolute
fool save the captain's life yeah i can do that easy what that's ludicrous
he'll destroy you did you not hear a word of that man you must really want to kill him huh
can't i at least try come on please be my guest thank you
whoa i've never felt this much anti-magic in one place before
for every action taken in this life there must always be consequences
you should do your best to remember that you should do your best to remember that human
wait this
where am i
i must be inside his memories or his
soul or something like that maybe everything the sword sucked out is flowing into me
so loud
my head's killing me
time magic was enough to save them
impressive though it would appear you used all the time and power you had saved us
you would have seen with the tag of mine coming but unfortunately you weren't able to call off that
final time magic spell in order to get out of the way because you're the wizard king
wizard king wizard king
i allowed myself to be deceived for licht's sake
it was a mistake to resurrect the elves so many sacrifices that he didn't even want
i made a mistake i was never chosen in the first place humans are evil or is that just what i
wanted to believe if it's true then that means no william and i understood each other
we can't have understanding humans do this
it's why i hate them
forgive them all humans are monsters
that's right everything is their fault
i knew i'd find you eventually
you and i need to talk okay pal name's asta i'm surprised on the inside you're just a kid who's about
my age i never would have guessed it stay back you human what do you want
i get it you were tricked you couldn't protect the ones you loved and everything you once believed
in was lost you're dealing with so many crazy feelings you can't stand it anymore
but that's why i have to tell you this don't you dare give up again
all you've ever done is give up instead of facing your problems you locked yourself away and hid in
the darkness because you thought it was the easiest thing to do
no don't don't talk to me shut up i don't have to listen to a thing you'd say
you could never understand stupid human
enough with this human crap i told you my name's asta answer me how dare you kill the wizard king
he was a great man and everyone respected him i wanted to be like him one day we all did
and you took control of all those magic knights when you brought back the elves you hurt tons
of innocent people you say you can't forgive humans well i can never forgive you but that's why
we and now after all you did you're acting like this just because you made a mistake that you can't fix
that doesn't mean you're allowed to run away and cry think about it shouldn't you be trying to
defeat that creepy devil guy too you had the guts to make everything else happen right you did that
maybe you weren't chosen maybe no one wanted you and maybe you can't be forgiven but you still have
to stand your ground without making excuses for yourself what i don't understand you at all
why are you trying so hard to change my mind i know you're wrong leave me alone
i wasn't chosen no one wanted me i've screwed some stuff up but i made up my mind
i'm gonna be the wizard king that's why
that's why as long as you're alive i won't give up on you you sound like him let's foster understanding
i don't believe it that runt brought pottery back honestly you must be the most foolish human i've ever
met say that again i dare you okay looks like we'll have to wait to bring captain vengeance out
right now there's one thing i can do
if you'll help me we can end this once and for all i'm in
no way am i letting that evil lunatic get what he wants
i guess this is it the door to the outside now then
not yet face me demon look at you lobbing threats at me when you're not even fully awakened
seems somebody's holding a garage i suppose i can't blame you we have quite a tumultuous history
and now i've taken the grimoire of someone very dear to you and made it my own
whoa i didn't expect you to have so much fight left in you since your soul's still unstable after
spawning that demon i'm impressed as a reward for your hard work i'm going to give you a proper death
and earth shield
now tempest of blaze
split them open
next up here's mine
that sword can absorb magic but sadly i imagine it doesn't offer much protection against more
concrete attacks like this iron lance with the use of word soul magic i can make anything happen by
speaking it into existence and i can also summon physical matter look at you with your little sword
you're no threat to me at all goodbye leader of the elves
oh my seems we have an elf who wasn't an apostle of sephora i noticed babel heading into the shadow palace
so i decided to follow him when i got inside and found him unconscious i knew that something must have gone
wrong
devil i'll stop you
did you say devil i'm not so sure i mean if devils are even a real thing
he's not one he's way too wimpy
looks like nozel went toward that other strong magic i sensed so i'm glad i came this way something
crazy's going on with this key
so many of you we've got ourselves a party man this guy reeks of malice
human you came this far just to get in my way
can we skip the playful banter and get this done i don't have time to listen to you flatter yourself
you're obviously not the biggest baddie in the room
if you can't keep up with me i'm letting you die
hey now you're starting to sound like the prickly princess i remember
try to keep her body in one piece till she gets back
dark magic black hole dark cloak lightless slash
what masterful teamwork
and there i thought you two wouldn't be on the best of terms right now
i'm as shocked as you are
as if you rosy
i hope you're not
is
影を広げた
まだ止まない雨 居場所を示す
足跡はやがて消えてしまうから
新しいページを今開こう
恐れずに 先頭で旗を振った
向かいが強いほど 高くまで飛べるから
Just take my hand 今日を生きる君に
明日が待っている
クロブリケット
you ladies we're supposed to do it in unison here yeah i think he's fine he's our savior
we need to be careful with him what's with that bird okay okay we can take a quick break
huh narrow the old demon's bones take me there
narrow can talk then again i was out cold so maybe i was just dreaming can somebody please
pinch my cheek really hard black clover page 117 breaking the seal ow nope not a dream narrow can
talk